[
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 4/5 + 9/5?",
    "choice1": "5/5",
    "choice2": "13/5",
    "choice3": "14/5",
    "choice4": "1 entero 3/5",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 4/3 + 1/3?",
    "choice1": "5/3",
    "choice2": "1 entero",
    "choice3": "3/3",
    "choice4": "1 entero 1/3",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 2/7 - 1/7?",
    "choice1": "0",
    "choice2": "1/7",
    "choice3": "3/7",
    "choice4": "1 entero",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 4/5 - 1/5?",
    "choice1": "2/5",
    "choice2": "4/5",
    "choice3": "3/5",
    "choice4": "5/5",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "¿A cuanto equivale 1 entero + 3/5?",
    "choice1": "1 entero 4/5",
    "choice2": "8/5",
    "choice3": "6/5",
    "choice4": "2/5",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 5/3 + 2/2?",
    "choice1": "7/3",
    "choice2": "8/2",
    "choice3": "5/4",
    "choice4": "8/3",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿A cuanto equivale 8/4 - 3/2?",
    "choice1": "1 entero 3/4",
    "choice2": "11/4",
    "choice3": "1/2",
    "choice4": "5/4",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 1 entero 1/5 - 2/10?",
    "choice1": "4/5",
    "choice2": "1 entero",
    "choice3": "7/5",
    "choice4": "8/10",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "¿Cuanto es 4/4 + 5/6?",
    "choice1": "10/4",
    "choice2": "1/6",
    "choice3": "1 entero 1/4",
    "choice4": "11/6",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "¿A cuanto equivale 9/7 + 4/14?",
    "choice1": "3/3",
    "choice2": "15/14",
    "choice3": "11/7",
    "choice4": "10/9",
    "answer": 3
  }
]
